Joaquín Serra Caggiano

Valencia, Spain · Portfolio · +34 624 750 408 · joaquincaggiano@gmail.com

Developer with experience in creating custom software. I specialize in the design and implementation of mobile applications (iOS, Android) and web pages. Offering efficient and scalable products adapted to the needs of each project.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Desaway Valencia, Spain

Frontend Developer

December 2023-Currently

- Development of custom mobile applications and web pages, adapting them to the unique needs of each project. Each product was designed from scratch, with personalized logic, ensuring innovative and functional solutions.
- **Comprehensive project development,** from the interpretation of mockups to the implementation of styles and functionalities in the interface. Ensuring that the user experience is consistent with the design vision, transforming ideas into interactive and engaging final products.
- **Main focus on frontend**, developing fluid and visually appealing user interfaces, using modern technologies such as Next.Js and React Native. However, I also **manage backend functionalities**, such as the creation of databases, the implementation of schemas in Prisma and the management of our own APIs to ensure the correct functionality of the product.
- Management of application documentation, ensuring that the processes and solutions implemented are well described. Facilitating maintenance and future expansions, improving team efficiency in long-term project management.
- **Collaboration with the design team,** ensuring an excellent user experience regarding aesthetics and functionality.
- **Development of personalized and innovative projects,** promoting the improvement of technical skills and constant learning. Each project is presented as a unique challenge, which implies an opportunity for professional growth in multiple areas of development.

Coder HouseBackend Tutor

Buenos Aires, Argentina

June 2023–September 2023

- Guide students in the learning process, accompanying them in the understanding and application
 of fundamental concepts and good development practices.
- **Correction of exercises,** offering detailed feedback on them. With the aim that they not only solve the problems raised, but also improve in writing code, obtaining a cleaner, more efficient and scalable solution.
- **Resolution of technical and conceptual doubts,** with the objective that students understand the theory and its application in practice.
- **Accompaniment during the learning process**, providing technical support and collaborating in creating a proactive mentality towards backend learning.

EDUCATION

UDEMY

SOLID principles July 2024 - August 2024

UDEMY

Rosario, Argentina July 2023 - November 2023 React Native course

Rosario, Argentina

UDEMY Rosario, Argentina

February 2023 - July 2023 Next.Js course

UDEMY Rosario, Argentina React course August 2022 - January 2023

UDEMY Rosario, Argentina

Javascript course June 2022 - July 2022

DIGITAL HOUSE Rosario, Argentina Full Stack developer May 2021 - May 2022

UNIVERSIDAD ABIERTA INTERAMERICANA Rosario, Argentina Other studies not related to computing April 2016 - March 2021

SKILLS

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- React Native
- Next.Js
- Next UI
- Node.Js
- Prisma ORM
- Express.js
- PostgreSQL
- Next Auth
- Git
- MobX State Tree